<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Intrust Communications</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="menu_services">Services</string>
    <string name="menu_clients">Clients</string>
    <string name="menu_careers">Careers</string>
    <string name="menu_contact_us">Contact us</string>
    <string name="menu_map">Where we are</string>

    <string name="works_list">
        <li>Lead Generation</li>\n
        <li>Telemarketing</li>\n
        <li>Remote Office</li>\n
        <li>Customer Service</li>
    </string>

    <string name="client_benefits_list_webchat_page">
        <li>Significant reduction in costs as amount of telephone support calls is low</li>\n\n
        <li>Ability to handle more than one customer whilst at all times respecting Data Protection and Compliance</li>\n\n
        <li>We can provide 24 hour Live Web Chat support services</li>\n\n
        <li>Provide real-time contact solutions that will increase conversions and improve customer satisfaction levels</li>
    </string>

    <string name="intrust_operate_as_follow_inbound_page">
        <li>Providing high quality, Customer interaction for Customer Service and Sales calls</li>\n\n
        <li>Working with our clients to have fully synced calendars where appropriate</li>\n\n
        <li>Increase your sales and Customer Interaction today and contact <b>Intrust Communications</b></li>
    </string>

    <string name="intrust_operate_as_follow_customer_retention">
        <li>We will work with you to suggest ways/incentivies to either win your customers back or maintain them within the business</li>\n\n
        <li>We will work with you to provide comprehensive feedback on why your customer felt the need to leave in the first place</li>\n\n
        <li>We will work with you to provide a plan to ensure your customers are always kept happy and maintained with your business</li>\n\n
        <li>Subject to client agreement we can make a follow up call after winback/ recontract to measure the success and provide comprehensive feedback to you</li>
    </string>

    <string name="client_benefits_list_inbound_page">
        <li>Flexibility to create a bespoke service for your business requirements</li>\n\n
        <li>Responsive, professional and cost-effective solutions</li>\n\n
        <li>High-quality customer interactions and a high return on Investment</li>\n\n
        <li>Experience across a wide range of sectors, media and languages</li>\n\n
        <li>Continuous real-time monitoring and reporting of your KPIs that generate the highest level of qualified leads</li>\n\n
        <li>High response rates with successful up-selling and cross-selling programs</li>\n\n
        <li>Experts in this Industry and will work with you as our client to improve the overall Customer Journey</li>
    </string>

    <string name="intrust_operate_as_follow_lead_page">
        <li>Providing high quality, fully confirmed leads to our clients.</li>\n\n
        <li>Working with our clients and have fully synced calendars where appropriate.</li>\n\n
        <li>A text or phone call will be made 24 hours before the appointment (working day) to confirm everything is still in order.</li>\n\n
        <li>Subject to client agreement we can make a follow up call after the appointment to measure the success and provide comprehensive feedback to our client.</li>
    </string>

    <string name="list_back_office_page">
        <li>Postage of Letters</li>\n\n
        <li>Shipping of packages from merchandise material (Mugs, Pens) through to bigger packages such as crates of wine etc.</li>
    </string>

    <string name="lead_generation_last_para">We will work with you to set and agree a plan of action that will ensure your sales Increase and your sales pipeline is maintained.  An agreed criteria to Generate Leads and appointments for you that will ensure you get a return on your investment.<b> All of this can be done in a cost effective way.</b></string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
